Guide to the Congregational Church Records
Yale University Divinity School Library
- Congregational Churches in the United States: Regional, State, and Local Records, Series V
  - Iowa
    - Intrastate organizations and meetings
      - Grinnell Association, 1951, 1952, n.d. (Box 65, Folder 249)
      - North Central Association, 1944 (Box 65, Folder 249)
      - Northeastern Association, 1945 (Box 65, Folder 249)
      - Southwestern Association, 1946 (Box 65, Folder 249)
      - Webster City Association, 1942 (Box 65, Folder 249)
    - Individual Churches
      - Bradford: First Congregational Church, ca. 1925 (Box 16, Folder 95)
      - Clinton: First Congregational Church, 1874 (Box 16, Folder 95)
      - Council Bluffs: Congregational Church, 1872 (Box 16, Folder 95)
      - Des Moines: Plymouth Church, 1882 (Box 16, Folder 95)
      - Dubuque: Congregational Church, 1849 (Box 16, Folder 95)
      - Fayette: Congregational Church, 1897 (Box 16, Folder 95)
      - Osage: First Congregational Church, 1900 (Box 16, Folder 95)
  - Kansas
    - Statewide organizations and meetings
      - General Association, 1877, 1903 (Box 16, Folder 97A)
      - Congregational and Christian Conference, 1946 (Box 65, Folder 250)
  - Louisiana (see also: Regional Associations: South-Western)
    - Statewide Organizations and Meetings
      - Minutes of Congregational Association, 1883, 1884 (Box 16, Folder 98)
  - Maine
    - Statewide Organizations and Meetings
      - Minutes of General Conference, 1828-1842 (Box 57, Folder v.17)
      - Minutes of General Conference, 1843-1857 (Box 57, Folder v.18)
      - Minutes of General Conference, 1858-1865 (Box 57, Folder v.19)
      - Minutes of General Conference, 1866-1867 (Box 57, Folder v.20)
      - Minutes of General Conference and Maine Missionary Society, 1868-1871 (Box 57, Folder v.20)
      - Minutes of General Conference and Maine Missionary Society, 1872-1876 (Box 57, Folder v.21)
      - Minutes of General Conference and Maine Missionary Society, 1877-1891 (Box 17, Folder 99)
      - Minutes of General Conference and Maine Missionary Society, 1892-1913 (Box 18, Folder 100)
      - "Brief address at the General Conference of Maine", n.d. (Box 65, Folder 251)
      - Minutes, by-laws of Congregational - Christian Conference, 1937-1961 (Box 19, Folder 101)
    - Intrastate Organizations and Meetings
      - Cumberland County Association, 1814, 1888 (Box 19, Folder 102)
      - Cumberland Association, 1945 (Box 65, Folder 251)
    - Individual Churches (see: Record Group 48)
  - Massachusetts
    - Statewide Organizations and Meetings
      - Minutes of General Association, 1814, 1828, 1829, 1830 (Box 20, Folder 103)
      - Minutes of General Association, 1836, 1838-1840 (Box 20, Folder 104)
      - Minutes of General Association, 1841, 1843-1845 (Box 20, Folder 105)
      - Minutes of General Association, 1850, 1857-1859 (Box 21, Folder 106)
      - Minutes of General Association, 1860-1862, 1864 (Box 21, Folder 107)
      - Minutes of General Association, 1866-1871, 1873-1878, 1880-1886, 1890-1892 (Box 22, Folder 108)
      - Minutes of General Association, 1893-1894, 1898 (Box 22, Folder 109)
      - Minutes of General Conference, 1860-1867 (Box 58, Folder v.22)
      - Minutes of Massachusetts Congregational Conference, 1917, 1926, 1927 (Box 23, Folder 110)
      - Minutes of Massachusetts Congregational Conference and Missionary Society, 1928-1934 (Box 23, Folder 111)
      - MMCCMC, 1935-1939 (Box 58, Folder v.23)
      - MMCCMC, 1940-1944 (Box 58, Folder v.24)
      - MMCCMC, 1945-1949 (Box 58, Folder v.25)
      - MMCCMC, 1950-1952 (Box 58, Folder v.26)
      - MMCCMC: By-laws, 1950 (Box 64, Folder 232)
      - Minutes of Massachusetts Congregational Christian Conference, 1953-1954 (Box 59, Folder v.26)
      - Minutes of Massachusetts Congregational Christian Conference, 1955-1959 (Box 59, Folder v.27)
      - Minutes of Massachusetts Congregational Christian Conference, 1960-1963 (Box 59, Folder v.28)
      - Ecclesiastical Council, Brimfield, 1801 (Box 23, Folder 112)
      - Ecclesiastical Council, Fall River, 1842 (Box 23, Folder 112)
      - Communication of the General Association, 1809 (Box 23, Folder 112)
      - Congregational Charitable Society, 1815 (Box 23, Folder 112)
      - Home Evangelization State Commission on, 1867-1871 (Box 23, Folder 112A)
      - Boston: Congregational Board of Publication, 1855-1859 (Box 23, Folder 112B)
      - Massachusetts Convention of Congregational Ministers, 1831 (Box 64, Folder 231)
    - Intrastate Organizations and Meetings
      - Barnstable Association, 1866, 1912, n.d. (Box 24, Folder 113)
      - Berkshire: Association, 1849 (Box 24, Folder 113)
      - Berkshire: Berkshire North Association, n.d. (Box 64, Folder 229)
      - Brookfield Association, ca. 1949 (Box 64, Folder 229)
      - Congregational Church Union of Boston and Vicinity, 1905 (Box 24, Folder 114)
      - Essex: Essex North Association, ca. 1946 (Box 64, Folder 229)
      - Essex: Essex South Association, 1945 (Box 64, Folder 229)
      - Franklin Association, 1936 (Box 64, Folder 229)
      - Hampden Conference and Benevolent Association of Congregational Churches, 1870-1874, 1876-1877 (Box 24, Folder 115)
      - HCBACC, 1879-1893, 1897, 1910-1911 (Box 24, Folder 116)
      - HCBACC, 1945 (Box 64, Folder 230)
      - Hampshire Association, 1932, 1938 (Box 64, Folder 227)
      - Middlesex-Mendon Association, 1944 (Box 64, Folder 227)
      - Middlesex Union Association, n.d. (Box 64, Folder 227)
      - Old Colony United Association, n.d. (Box 64, Folder 228)
      - Pilgrim Association, 1938, 1944 (Box 64, Folder 228)
      - South Berkshire Association, 1927 (Box 64, Folder 228)
      - Suffolk: Association, 1849, 1898 (Box 24, Folder 117)
      - Suffolk: Suffolk North Association, 1931 (Box 64, Folder 226)
      - Suffolk: Suffolk South Association, 1943 (Box 64, Folder 226)
      - Suffolk: Suffolk West Association, 1940 (Box 64, Folder 226)
      - Taunton Conference, 1902 (Box 24, Folder 118)
      - Worcester: Conference and Association, 1876, 1884, 1947 (Box 24, Folder 119)
      - Worcester: Worcester South Association, n.d. (Box 64, Folder 225)
      - Worcester: Worcester North Association, 1940 (Box 64, Folder 225)
      - Worcester: Worcester Central Association, 1944 (Box 64, Folder 225)
      - Congregational Club, Boston Necrology for, 1893 (Box 24, Folder 119A)
      - Middlesex Union Conference, 1860 1867, 1877 (Box 24, Folder 119B)
    - Individual Churches (see: Record Group 48)
  - Michigan
    - Statewide organizations and meetings
      - Minutes of General Association, 1842, 1843, 1848, 1851, 1852, 1854 (Box 25, Folder 120)
      - Minutes of General Association, 1856, 1857, 1860, 1862, 1864, 1865 (Box 25, Folder 121)
      - Minutes of General Association, 1867, 1872, 1895 (Box 25, Folder 122)
      - Minutes of Congregational Conference, 1911, 1912, 1914-1917 (Box 25, Folder 123)
      - Papers read at Congregational Association annual meeting, 1904 (Box 25, Folder 124)
      - Congregational and Christian Conference, 1949 (Box 65, Folder 252)
    - Intrastate organizations and meetings
      - Stanton Council, 1882 (Box 25, Folder 124A)
    - Individual Churches
      - Detroit: First Congregational Church, 1894 (Box 26, Folder 125)
      - Ann Arbor: First Congregational Church, 1947 (Box 26, Folder 125A)
      - Grand Rapids: First Congregational Church, 1854 (Box 26, Folder 125A)
      - Olivet: First Congregational Church, 1894 (Box 26, Folder 125A)
      - Southfield: North Congregational Church, 1958 (Box 26, Folder 125A)
  - Minnesota
    - Statewide organizations and Meetings
      - Minutes of General Congregational Association, 1906 (Box 26, Folder 126)
      - Congregational Christian Conference, n.d. (Box 65, Folder 254)
    - Individual Churches
      - Owatonna: Associated Church (Congregational- Presbyterian), 1919 (Box 26, Folder 127)
      - Minneapolis: Plymouth Congregational Church, 1887 (Box 26, Folder 127A)
  - Missouri
    - Statewide Organizatoins and Meetings
      - Minutes of General Conference, 1866, 1867 (Box 27, Folder 128)
      - Minutes of General or Congregational Association, 1870-1885, 1889 (Box 27, Folder 129)
      - Minutes of General or Congregational Association, 1890, 1891, 1894, 1896, 1901, 1907-1909 (Box 27, Folder 130)
      - Minutes of Congregational Conference, 1910, 1912, 1920-1924, 1926 (Box 28, Folder 131)
      - Congregational Christian Conference, n.d. (Box 65, Folder 253)
    - Individual Churches
      - Saint Louis: Fifth Congregational Church, 1884 (Box 28, Folder 132)
      - Saint Louis: First Congregational Church, 1852, 1874 (Box 28, Folder 132)
      - Saint Louis: Pilgrim Congregational Church, 1881, 1910-1914 (Box 28, Folder 133)
      - Saint Louis: Compton Hill Congregational Church, 1891 (Box 28, Folder 133)
  - Montana
    - Statewide organizations and meetings
      - Minutes of Congregational Conference, 1954 (Box 28, Folder 134)
    - Intrastate organizations and meetings
      - Minutes of General Association, 1876, 1878, 1889, 1891-1902 (Box 29, Folder 135)
      - Minutes of Congregational Conference, 1910-1926 (Box 30, Folder 136)
      - Minutes of Congregational Conference, 1927, 1929-1944, 1946-1962 (Box 31, Folder 137)
  - New Hampshire
    - Statewide organizations and meetings
      - Minutes of General Association, 1809, 1812, 1813, 1818-1820 (Box 32, Folder 138)
      - Minutes of General Association, 1821-1825 (Box 32, Folder 139)
      - Minutes of General Association, 1826-1834 (Box 32, Folder 140)
      - Minutes of General Association, 1835-1837, 1839, 1841-1849 (Box 33, Folder 141)
      - Minutes of General Association, 1850-1860 (Box 33, Folder 142)
      - Minutes of General Association, 1861-1885 (Box 34, Folder 143)
      - Minutes of General Association, 1887-1908 (Box 35, Folder 144)
      - Minutes of General Conference, 1909-1928, 1930-1932 (Box 36, Folder 145)
      - Congregational - Christian Conference, 1933-1935, 1947-1961 (Box 37, Folder 146)
      - Ecclesiastical Council, Exeter, 1842 (Box 37, Folder 147)
    - Individual Churches (see: Record Group 48)
  - New Jersey
    - Statewide organizations and meetings
      - Minutes of Congregational Association, 1887, 1895-1897, 1905, 1908 (Box 38, Folder 148)
      - Minutes of Congregational Conference, 1910-1913 (Box 38, Folder 149)
      - Program: 42nd Annual Meeting, 1909 (Box 38, Folder 150)
      - Association of Congregational-Christian Churches, 1945 (Box 65, Folder 256)
      - Minutes of General Association, 1871, 1872 (Box 38, Folder 150A)
    - Individual Churches
      - East Orange: Grove Street Congregational Church, 1868 (Box 38, Folder 151)
      - Jersey City: First Congregational Church, 1916 (Box 38, Folder 151)
      - Montclair: First Congregational Church, 1903 (Box 67, Folder 3)
      - Montclair: First Congregational Church, 1916 (Box 38, Folder 151)
      - Orange Valley Church, 1867 (Box 38, Folder 151)
      - Orange: Congregational Church, 1860 (Box 38, Folder 151)
      - West Orange: Second Valley Church, 1867 (Box 67, Folder 24)
  - New Mexico
    - Statewide organizations and meetings
      - Minutes of Congregational Conference, 1917 (Box 38, Folder 152)
  - New York (See also: Regional Organizations and Meetings)
    - Statewide organizations and meetings
      - Minutes of General Association, 1835, 1837-1844, 1847 (Box 38, Folder 153)
      - Minutes of General Association, 1848-1877, 1879-1886, 1888-1891 (Box 39, Folder 154)
      - Minutes of General Association, 1892-1896, 1898-1901 (Box 39, Folder 155)
      - Minutes of Congregational Association, 1902, 1904-1906, 1908-1909 (Box 40, Folder 156)
      - Minutes of Congregational - Christian Conference, 1944, 1958, 1961, 1962 (Box 40, Folder 157)
      - Essays, Constitution, Programme of General Association, 1937, 1878, 1894 (Box 40, Folder 157A)
      - New York Conference, 1982 (Box 40, Folder 157A)
    - Intrastate organizations and meetings
      - Albany Congregational Convention, 1856 (Box 40, Folder 157B)
      - Brooklyn Advisory Council, 1876 (Box 40, Folder 158)
      - Brooklyn Council, 1874, 1876 (Box 40, Folder 158A)
      - Congregational Association of New York and Brooklyn, 1848 (Box 40, Folder 158)
      - Congregational Association of Western New York, 1901 (Box 40, Folder 158)
      - Congregational Church Building Society, 1910-1913 (Box 40, Folder 158)
      - Congregational Church Extension Society of New YorkCity and Brooklyn, 1895 (Box 40, Folder 158)
      - Congregational Club of New York and Vicinity, 1930 (Box 40, Folder 158)
      - New York City Congregational Church Association, 1948 (Box 40, Folder 158)
      - Oneida Association, 1827 (Box 40, Folder 158A)
      - Orleans and Niagara Association, 1847 (Box 40, Folder 158A)
      - Western Association of Congregational Christian Churches and Ministers, 1941 (Box 40, Folder 257)
    - Individual Churches
      - Brooklyn: Clinton Avenue Congregational Church, 1859, 1872 (Box 41, Folder 159)
      - Brooklyn: Plymouth Church, 1870-1911 (Box 41, Folder 160)
      - Brooklyn: Tompkins Avenue Congregational Church, 1886, 1905 (Box 41, Folder 161)
      - Brooklyn: Park Congregational Church, 1905 (Box 41, Folder 161)
      - Canandaigua: First Congregational Church, 1852, 1863, 1867 (Box 41, Folder 161)
      - Eldred: First Congregational Church, 1899 (Box 41, Folder 161)
      - Franklin: First Congregational Church, 1842 (Box 64, Folder 235)
      - Homer: Congregational Church and Society, 1901, n.d. (Box 41, Folder 161A)
      - Jamestown: First Congregational Church, n.d. (Box 41, Folder 161A)
      - Mount Vernon: First Congregational Church, 1892 (Box 41, Folder 162)
      - New York City: Broadway Tabernacle, 1863, n.d. (Box 41, Folder 163)
      - New York City: Church of the Atonement, 1869 (Box 41, Folder 163)
      - New York City: Church of the Pilgrims, 1869-1876 (Box 41, Folder 163A)
      - New York City: Church of the Puritans, 1848, 1850, 1857, 1859, 1860 (Box 41, Folder 164)
      - New York City: Church of the Puritans, 1859-1860 (Box 67, Folder 4)
      - New York City: Harlem Congregational Church, 1879 (Box 41, Folder 165)
      - New York City: Madison Avenue Congregational Church, 1884 (Box 41, Folder 166)
      - New York City: Manhattan Congregational Church, 1898, 1899, 1901, 1903, 1904 (Box 41, Folder 166)
      - New York City: Memorial Church, 1862 (Box 41, Folder 166)
      - New York City: New England Church, 1866 (Box 41, Folder 167)
      - New York City: Old First Church, 1914, 1915 (Box 41, Folder 167)
      - New York City: South Church, 1887 (Box 41, Folder 167)
      - New York City: Trinity Congregational Church, n.d. (Box 41, Folder 167)
      - Portchester: Congregational Church, ca. 1887 (Box 41, Folder 167)
      - Poughkeepsie: Church of the Holy Comforter, 1909 (Box 42, Folder 168)
      - Poughkeepsie: First Congregational Church, 1877-1914 (Box 42, Folder 168)
      - Sherburne: First Congregational Church, 1887 (Box 42, Folder 169)
      - Spencerport: Congregational Church, 1863 (Box 42, Folder 169)
      - Walton: First Congregational Church, 1866 (Box 42, Folder 169)
      - Walton: Second Congregational Church (Box 42, Folder 169)
  - North Dakota
    - Statewide organizations and meetings
      - Minutes of Congregational Conference, 1916 (Box 43, Folder 170)
      - Proceedings and Reports of Congregational Conference, 1923-1926 (Box 43, Folder 171)
      - Congregational Christian Conference, 1937 (Box 65, Folder 258)
    - Intrastate organizations and meetings
      - Proposed constitution: Southeastern, Northwestern, Northeastern, Southwestern Associations, 1937 (Box 65, Folder 258)
  - Ohio
    - Statewide organizations and meetings
      - Minutes of Congregational Conference, 1852, 1857, 1861, 1864, 1871-1873 (Box 43, Folder 172)
      - Minutes of Congregational Conference, 1875, 1877, 1878 (Box 43, Folder 173)
      - Minutes of Congregational Conference, 1908, 1909, 1916, 1922-1924, 1926, 1929 (Box 45, Folder 177)
      - Minutes of Congregational Association, 1880-1886 (Box 43, Folder 174)
      - Minutes of Congregational Association, 1888-1895 (Box 44, Folder 175)
      - Minutes of Congregational Association, 1896-1904 (Box 44, Folder 176)
      - Minutes of Conference of Congregational Christian Churches, 1932, 1934-1939, 1942, 1944, 1945 (Box 45, Folder 178)
      - Minutes of Conference of Congregational Christian Churches, 1948-1963 (Box 46, Folder 179)
      - Basis of Fellowship and Rules: Conference of Congregational Christian Churches, 1949 (Box 46, Folder 179A)
      - Bureau of Finance Report, 1913 (Box 46, Folder 180)
    - Intrastate organizations and meetings
      - Median Association 75th Anniversary Session, 1927 (Box 46, Folder 181)
      - Puritan Association and Conference, 1854 (Box 46, Folder 181)
    - Individual Churches
      - Chatham: Congregational Church, 1884 (Box 67, Folder 20)
      - Cincinnati: First Evangelical Congregational Church, 1946 (Box 46, Folder 182)
      - Cincinnati: First Orthodox Congregational Church, 1864 (Box 46, Folder 182)
      - Cincinnati: First United Church, 1945 (Box 46, Folder 182)
      - Cincinnati: Walnut Hills Congregational Church, 1935, 1936 (Box 46, Folder 182)
      - Cleveland: Euclid Avenue Congregational Church, 1893 (Box 46, Folder 182)
      - Cleveland: Pilgrim Church, 1894 (Box 46, Folder 182)
      - Columbus: First Congregational Church, 1902 (Box 46, Folder 182A)
      - Elyria: First Congregational Church, 1945 (Box 46, Folder 182A)
      - Madison: Madison Church, n.d. (Box 46, Folder 182A)
      - Mansfield: First Congregational Church, 1891 (Box 46, Folder 182A)
      - Painesville: First Church, 1885 (Box 46, Folder 182A)
      - Strongsville: First Congregational Church, 1917 (Box 46, Folder 182A)
      - Toledo: Washington Street Congregational Church, 1889 (Box 46, Folder 182A)
  - Oregon
    - Statewide organizations and meetings
      - Proceedings of Congregational Conference, 1935 (Box 47, Folder 183)
      - Constitution and By-Laws: Congregational Conference, 1950 (Box 65, Folder 259)
    - Intrastate organizations and meetings
      - East Willamette Association, 1951 (Box 65, Folder 259)
  - Pennsylvania
    - Statewide organizations and meetings
      - Conference of Congregational and Christian Churches, 1948 (Box 65, Folder 260)
    - Intrastate organizations and meetings
      - Association of Congregational and Christian Churches of Northeastern Pennsylvania, 1945 (Box 65, Folder 261)
      - Philadelphia Association of Congregational Christian Churches, n.d. (Box 65, Folder 261)
      - Rays Hill and Southern Pennsylvania Association of Congregational Christian Churches (Box 65, Folder 261)
      - Western Pennsylvania Association of Congregational Christian Churches and Minister (Box 65, Folder 261)
    - Individual Churches
      - Johnston: First Congregational Church, 1890 (Box 47, Folder 184)
      - Lansford: English Congregational Church, 1921 (Box 47, Folder 184)
      - Pittsburgh: German Evangelical Protestant Smithfield Church (Congregational), 1932 (Box 47, Folder 184)
      - Philadelphia: The Central Congregational Church of Philadelphia, 1894 (Box 47, Folder 184)
    - See also: Regional Organizations and Meetings
      - (Susquehanna Association), 1878 (Box 52, Folder 214)
  - Puerto Rico
    - Statewide organizations and meetings
      - Evangelical Congregational Conference of Puerto Rico, n.d. (Box 65, Folder 262)
  - Rhode Island
    - Statewide organizations and meetings
      - Proceedings of Evangelical Consociation and Home Missionary Society, 1834, 1836, 1838, 1845, 1847, 1848 (Box 47, Folder 185)
      - Minutes of Evangelical Consociation and Home Missionary Society, 1849, 1851-1855, 1857-1862 (Box 47, Folder 186)
      - Minutes of Congregational Conference and Home Missionary Society, 1864-1866, 1868, 1879 (Box 47, Folder 187)
      - Minutes of Congregational Conference and Home Missionary Society, 1881, 1892, 1912 (Box 47, Folder 188)
      - Minutes of Congregational Conference, 1933-1962 (Box 48, Folder 189)
      - Constitution of Congregational Conference, n.d. (Box 65, Folder 263)
      - Minutes of Congregational Christian Conference (United Church of Christ), 1963-1968 (Box 48, Folder 190)
    - Individual Churches (see: Record Group 48)
  - South Dakota
    - Statewide organizations and meetings
      - Minutes of Congregational General Association of Dakota, 1882, 1885, 1886, 1890 (Box 48, Folder 191)
      - Minutes of Congregational Conference, 1916, 1917, 1933-1940 (Box 48, Folder 192)
      - Minutes of Congregational Conference, 1942-1944, 1949, 1950 (Box 49, Folder 193)
      - By-Laws of Congregational Conference, 1942 (Box 65, Folder 264)
  - Texas
    - Statewide organizations and meetings
      - Proceedings of Conference of Congregational Ministers and Churches, 1915-1920 (Box 49, Folder 194)
      - Syllabus of Minutes of Conference of Congregational Ministers and Churches, 1924, 1926, 1927 (Box 49, Folder 195)
  - Utah
    - Statewide organizations and meetings
      - Minutes of General Congregational Association, 1882-1888, 1892 (Box 49, Folder 196)
      - Minutes, constitution of Congregational Conference, 1935-1938 (Box 49, Folder 197)
    - Individual churches
      - Provo: First Congregational Church, 1902 (Box 49, Folder 197)
  - Vermont
    - Statewide organizations and meetings
      Scope and Contents
      Including reports of Vermont Education Society through 1880 and of Vermont Domestic Missionary Society through 1961
      - Minutes of General Convention, 1795-1810 (published 1877) (Box 49, Folder 198)
      - Minutes of General Convention, 1819-1822, 1824, 1827-1829 (Box 49, Folder 199)
      - Minutes of General Convention, 1841-1854 (Box 59, Folder v.29)
      - Minutes of General Convention, 1855-1864 (Box 59, Folder v.30)
      - Minutes of General Convention, 1865-1870 (Box 59, Folder v.31)
      - Minutes of General Convention, 1871-1874 (Box 60, Folder v.32)
      - Minutes of General Convention, 1875-1877 (Box 60, Folder v.33)
      - Minutes of General Convention, 1878-1880 (Box 60, Folder v.34)
      - Minutes of General Convention, 1881-1884 (Box 60, Folder v.35)
      - Minutes of General Convention, 1885-1888 (Box 60, Folder v.35A)
      - Minutes of General Convention, 1889-1892 (Box 60, Folder v.36)
      - Minutes of General Convention, 1893-1896 (Box 60, Folder v.37)
      - Minutes of Congregational Convention, 1897-1900 (Box 61, Folder v.38)
      - Minutes of Congregational Convention, 1901-1904 (Box 61, Folder v.39)
      - Minutes of Congregational Convention, 1905-1908 (Box 61, Folder v.40)
      - Minutes of Congregational Conference, 1902-1912 (Box 61, Folder v.41)
      - Minutes of Congregational Conference, 1913-1916 (Box 61, Folder v.42)
      - Minutes of Congregational Conference, 1917-1920 (Box 61, Folder v.43)
      - Minutes of Congregational Conference, 1921-1924 (Box 61, Folder v.44)
      - Minutes of Congregational Conference, 1925-1928 (Box 61, Folder v.45)
      - Minutes of Congregational Conference, 1929-1932 (Box 62, Folder v.46)
      - Minutes of Congregational Conference, 1933-1937 (Box 62, Folder v.47)
      - Minutes of Congregational Conference, 1938-1942 (Box 62, Folder v.48)
      - Minutes of Congregational Conference, 1943-1945 (Box 62, Folder v.49)
      - Minutes of Congregational Conference, 1946-1949 (Box 62, Folder v.50)
      - Minutes of Congregational Conference, 1950-1953 (Box 62, Folder v.51)
      - Minutes of Congregational Conference, 1954-1957 (Box 62, Folder v.52)
      - Minutes of Congregational Conference, 1958-1961 (Box 62, Folder v.53)
      - Committee on Pastoral Sustentation, n.d. (Box 65, Folder 265)